A Guide to the Office of the Dean of Students Office Administrative Files, 1980-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Dean of Students, Office Administrative Files 1980-1989
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-18/2/1.901
This collection consists of 300 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions apply only to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred on 1990 October 22.
Scope and Content Information
Topical files from Dean Robert T. Canevari's office, chiefly on individual fraternities and sororities.
Organization
Series I: General Files, 1957-1986 Box 1
Series II: Fraternities, 1981-1986 Box 1-2
Series III: Sororities, 19841987 Box 2
Series IV: Restricted materials Box 3
Contents List
- Series I: General Files
  - Special Collections paperwork file 1990 (Box 1)
  - Derby days 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - F/S statistics 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Greek alumni program 1986 (Box 1)
  - Greek awards ceremony 1987 (Box 1)
  - Greek officer's orientation 1987 (Box 1)
  - Hazing--correspondence 1981-1985 (Box 1)
  - Housing and fire safety review board--annual report, form letters 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Inter-sorority council 1983-1985 (Box 1)
  - Membership development program--brochure 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - Membership development program--program requests completed 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - Parking and transportation 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Standards and procedures for the operation of F/S--miscellaneous 1957-1986 (Box 1)
  - Student evaluations 1984 (Box 1)
  - Trash concerns 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Series II: Fraternities
  - Alpha Delta Phi 1983-1986 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Phi Alpha 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Alpha Tau Omega 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Beta Theta Pi 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Chi Phi 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Chi Psi 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Delta Sigma Phi 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Delta Tau Delta 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Delta Upsilon 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Gamma Nu Psi 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Kappa Alpha 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Kappa Alpha Psi 1984-1986 (Box 1)
  - Kappa Sigma 1983-1986 (Box 1)
  - Omega Psi Phi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Phi Beta Sigma 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Phi Delta Theta 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Phi Epsilon Pi of ZBT [Zeta Beta Tau] 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Phi Gamma Delta 1981-1985 (Box 2)
  - Phi Kappa Psi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Pi Kappa Phi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Pi Lambda Phi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon 1982-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Alpha Mu 1981-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Chi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Delta Tau 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Nu 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Phi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Pi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - St. Anthony's Hall 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - St. Elmo's Hall 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Tau Kappa Epsilon 1982-1986 (Box 2)
  - Theta Chi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Theta Delta Chi 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Zeta Phi Beta 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Zeta Psi 1982-1986 (Box 2)
  - Zeta Tau Alpha 1984-1986 (Box 2)
- Series III: Sororities
  - Alpha Chi Omega 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Delta Pi 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Omicron Pi 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Alpha Phi 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Chi Omega 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Delta Delta Delta 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Delta Gamma 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Delta Sigma Theta 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Kappa Alpha Theta 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Kappa Delta 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Kappa Kappa Gamma 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Phi Mu 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Pi Beta Phi 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Sigma Sigma Sigma 1984-1986 (Box 2)
- Series IV: Restricted Materials (Box 3)